(quiet laugh)
(Penny:)Wow, I just felt this wave
(Penny:)of affection for you.
(Sheldon:)You sure it's not
too much Bible juice?
(Penny:)And the wave is gone.
(Zombie:)Brains!
Keep it down!
We're working here.
(Raj:)Okay, we've got
the cipher decoded!
(Emily:)How's it going
with the globe?
(Amy:)We used the coordinates
to locate the cities.
(Leonard:)I'm putting the city names
in the grid now.
(Leonard:)I'm sure that'll give us
the code to the safe.
(Zombie:)Solve puzzle too fast!
(Zombie:)Slow down!
Yup! Got the code.
(Baggage Clerk:)Just saying...
(Zombie:)no refund for finish early!
(Bernadette:)Sure you don't want to go home?
(Bernadette:)When the bag's returned,
they'll deliver it to us.
(Howard:)No, I'm not leaving without her.
(Bernadette:)All right, we'll wait.